Hello,Kira,how are you?
你好，基拉，最近好吗？
Fine thanks,Paul,how are you?
很好，谢谢，保罗，你最近好吗？
Well,thanks.It's good to see you.
很好，谢谢，见到你很高兴。
It must be twelve months since you did our course?
自从你上完我们的课程到现在已经有一年了？
That's right.It's nice to come back and say hello.
没错，回来再见面的感觉很好。
What course did you enrol in?
你参加的是什么课程？
Actually,I went straight into third year Pharmacy.
事实上，我直接上的是三年级药剂学。
They credited me with two years,which probably made it more difficult for me.
他们给了我两年的学分，这可能让我觉得更难了。
On the other hand,you were lucky to be granted credits.
另一方面，你能被授予学分很走运。
Is that why you chose the course?
这是你选择这门课的原因吗？
Yes.And,as I'd already finished a course in it in my country.
是的，另外我已经在我的国家完成了一门课程。
I thought it would be easier if I studied something I already knew.
我想如果我学一些我已知的知识会简单一些。
I didn't realise you went into third year.
我不知道你上的是三年级。
I thought you started in first year.
我以为你要从一年级开始学。
No wonder it was so hard!
怪不得会很难！
And what do you think is one of the big differences between studying at a university here and studying in your country?
你觉得在这里上大学和在你的国家上大学最大的区别之一是什么？
Well,I've found it very difficult to write assignments,because I wasn't familiar with that aspect of the system here.
我发现写作业很难，因为我不熟悉这边在这方面的体系是什么。
The main problem is that the lecturers expect you to be critical.
主要的问题是老师希望你具有批判性。
That made me feel really terrible.
这让我觉得很糟糕。
I thought "How can I possibly do it?
我想：“我怎么可能做这个？
How can I comment on someone else's research when they probably spent five years doing it?"
当他们可能花了5年做一个研究的时候，我怎么能对它提意见呢？”
I think a lot of people who come from overseas countries have similar problems.
我想许多留学生都和我有一样的问题，
But after a while it became easier for me.
但是过了一阵时间，这对我来说就很简单了。
People expect you to have problems with the process of reading and writing
人们认为你会在读写上有问题，
but,in fact,it is more a question of altering your viewpoint towards academic study.
但事实上，问题来自改变你对学术研究的观点。